{
    "id": "dd5b02abc73f443694b53b268869d2a1",
    "title": "Too And Enough",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There were ………………. many letters to write.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "enough",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3ae8202d83bf4d5aad79a17fbf8039d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea was ………………. It almost burnt my tongue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too hot",
                "hot too",
                "hot enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2f6df03bbd840f5986099113c2572d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Should I turn the heating on? I think the room isn’t ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too cool",
                "hot enough",
                "cool enough",
                "enough hot"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a0a2d36d845422b8437830e882971b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t buy the watch because it was ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough expensive",
                "too expensive",
                "expensive enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a6c00891daf4cad91aeed12827ede98"
        },
        {
            "question": "We didn’t buy the house because it was not …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too spacious",
                "enough spacious",
                "spacious enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7820bfc39ad84bb69788897c99c3d6e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you have a smaller size? This jacket is …………….. for me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough large",
                "large enough",
                "too large"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6d4a556bd6a4de886a932b865ce69f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some tablet computers are ………………… to fit inside your pocket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too small",
                "enough small",
                "small enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1386a6caabae4bd793401ebfcc6721ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bag was ………………….. for me to lift.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough heavy",
                "too heavy",
                "heavy enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7cafd500ae9646ae8475a8f04c90818a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………. to talk to them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough busy",
                "busy enough",
                "too busy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dc775243117e4c149b39ddbe45a629d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ………………. to take a vacation this year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too much time",
                "time enough",
                "enough time"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f7ac9ca74e1c48dbb836d8bb1b2ca7bd"
        }
    ]
}